

# Ibrahim Rabie

UI/UX Designer

### Education

### **High School Diploma**

Industrial School, Sharqia JUN 2015

Five Years studying Computer science

#### Bachelor of MIS

Obour Institute, Sharqia JUN 2019 graduated cum laude every year.

## Languages

Arabic Native

Very Good [Read, Write] **English** 

### Certificate

Foundations of User Experience (UX) Design **Verification Certification** 

Start the UX Design Process: Empathize, Define, and Ideate **Verification Certification** 

Build Wireframes and Low-Fidelity **Prototypes Verification Certification** 

## **Profile Summary**

Hello, I'm Ibrahim Rabie 26 Years.

Creative UI/UX Designer With More Than 2 Year Experience Facilitating and Supporting human interactions with complex systems and software. Maintains user-centric designs while adhering to prescribed interface principals. Dedicated to creating inviting interfaces for everything.

## **Work Experience**

### **UI/UX Designer**

Dipdux Analytica

FROM FEB 2021 TO PRESENT

Design user flows, wireframes, Information Architecture and User Interface for designs based on stakeholder requests and end-user feedback. Analyzed existing interfaces to detect user pain points.

### **UI/UX Designer**

Freelance

FROM JUN 2019 TO PRESENT

Design site maps, user flows, wireframes for designs based on stakeholder requests and end-user feedback. Analyzed existing interfaces to detect user pain points, recommending design changes and iterative updates

### Front-End Developer

Freelance

FROM MAY 2016 TO APR 2019

Designed and update layouts to meet usability, performance requirements and compatibility with multiple browsers using HTML,CSS,Javascript, Bootstartp, SASS.

## **Skills**

Software	Design	Strengths
Photoshop, Illustrator	Information Architecture	Collaboration
Adobe XD	Visual Design	Leadership
Figma	Wireframing	Problem Solving
Zeplin	User Stories	Critical thinking
MarvelApp [Mockup]	Responsive Design	Accessibility
HTML/CSS	Sketching	